export const questions = [
  {
    question: "What is the most popular programming language in 2023?",
    options: ["Java", "Python", "JavaScript", "C++"],
    answer: 2,
    createdBy: "Alice",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the full form of HTML?",
    options: [
      "Hyper Text Markup Language",
      "High Tech Machine Learning",
      "Home Tool Management Language",
      "Hyperloop Transport Management Language",
    ],
    answer: 0,
    createdBy: "Bob",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the output of the following code snippet?\n\n```console.log(typeof(1/0));```",
    options: ["undefined", "NaN", "Infinity", "-Infinity"],
    answer: 2,
    createdBy: "Charlie",
  },
  {
    question: "______ is the process of finding and fixing errors in code.",
    options: ["Debugging", "Compiling", "Testing", "Refactoring"],
    answer: 0,
    createdBy: "Alice",
  },
  {
    question: "JavaScript was created by _____.",
    options: ["Brendan Eich", "Steve Jobs", "Bill Gates", "Linus Torvalds"],
    answer: 0,
    createdBy: "Dave",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A database is a collection of _____ that can be accessed and manipulated by software.",
    options: ["spreadsheets", "files", "programs", "data"],
    answer: 3,
    createdBy: "Eve",
  },
  {
    question: "In CSS, what does the acronym 'CSS' stand for?",
    options: [
      "Cascading Style Sheets",
      "Computer Science Style",
      "Cascading Simple Syntax",
      "Computer System Styles",
    ],
    answer: 0,
    createdBy: "Bob",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the output of the following code snippet?\n\n```console.log(2 + '2');```",
    options: ["4", "22", "TypeError", "NaN"],
    answer: 1,
    createdBy: "Charlie",
  },
  {
    question:
      "______ refers to the practice of improving code after it has been written, without changing its functionality.",
    options: ["Debugging", "Testing", "Refactoring", "Compiling"],
    answer: 2,
    createdBy: "Dave",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is NOT a commonly used database management system?",
    options: ["MySQL", "PostgreSQL", "MongoDB", "Google Sheets"],
    answer: 3,
    createdBy: "Eve",
  },
  {
    question: "The acronym 'API' stands for:",
    options: [
      "Application Programming Interface",
      "Automated Process Interchange",
      "Access Point Indicator",
      "Application Performance Index",
    ],
    answer: 0,
    createdBy: "Alice",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a commonly used web browser?",
    options: ["Firefox", "Chrome", "Safari", "Microsoft Word"],
    answer: 3,
    createdBy: "Bob",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the output of the following code snippet?\n\n```console.log(5 == '5');```",
    options: ["true", "false", "TypeError", "NaN"],
    answer: 0,
    createdBy: "Charlie",
  },
];
